<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Happy New Year on ExiaHan&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.exiahan.com/tags/happy-new-year/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Happy New Year on ExiaHan&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 02:16:22 +0800</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://blog.exiahan.com/tags/happy-new-year/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Happy_Chinese_New_Year_In_2017</title>
      <link>https://blog.exiahan.com/posts/happy_chinese_new_year_in_2017/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 02:16:22 +0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.exiahan.com/posts/happy_chinese_new_year_in_2017/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h2 id=&#34;tldr&#34;&gt;TL;DR&lt;/h2&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Below is written by a man that with poor English skills. Read carefully if you really want to read.(But I will say thank you if you really read all the contents below. :) )&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Happy Chinese new year! In China, all the Chinese now say goodbye to the &amp;ldquo;Monkey Year&amp;rdquo; and step into the &amp;ldquo;year of Chicken&amp;rdquo;. Watching the Spring Festival Gala Evening provided by CCTV is a tradition for almost every Chinese. We watch the TV shows with families and share the stories that happend to each in Monkey Year.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;For me, it is the third year that my families celebrate the new year without my grandfather, who has gone in 2014. Still feel a little sad that I won&amp;rsquo;t have chance to hear my grandfather&amp;rsquo;s voice. And I also regret that I did&amp;rsquo;t capture any short videos for my grandfather when he is alive. Now what I can do is talk with my grandfather&amp;rsquo;s portrait.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In this year, there are lots of things happend to me: &lt;em&gt;Get a intership&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Pass the graduation thesis defense&lt;/em&gt;, &lt;em&gt;Get a third rewards in Alibaba&amp;rsquo;s Security Competition&lt;/em&gt; and also, &lt;em&gt;Re-Become a single doge. :)&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;But I am still a student now, and this may be my last school-days if I can not get a chance to pursue PhD.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Review the past yesr, I still have a lot of things to do but in fact I did not complete them. So in this year I will try my best to complete what I should have complete in 2016.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;First is Tofel. If you do read what I have written above, you will know my English skil need be improved. So I set a aim that to score at least 90 points in Tofel. To realize this, I will spend 2 hours to study English every day. Include reading, listening and speaking.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Second is technique in computer science. There still lots of knowledge I have to study like Compiler-Engineer, Crypto-and-Decrypto, Security and Algorithms. It may be boring to study these, but I will complete  them, and I must will.&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;And the last is to have a girl friend. Yeah, may it is a dream, but may there will be a beauty like me in this year.:)&lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;In the end, thank you for reading the so called English article I written above. Hope u a happy Chinese New Year, no matter whether u are a Chinese or a foreigner.:)&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>